{
    "id": "116cd70104644a9dabc95a2965b21f73",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was driving ……………………… and crashed into the car in front.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carefully",
                "carelessly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the tiger appeared from nowhere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Suddenly",
                "Slowly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain poured ………………………. and we took shelter under a tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heavily",
                "lightly",
                "slightly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher told a funny story and the children laughed ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loudly",
                "softly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The dancers performed ……………………. and we all clapped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gracefully",
                "clumsily"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you shouting ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loudly",
                "quietly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a golden voice. She sings ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beautifully",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t take a decision …………………………… Think it over for sometime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hastily",
                "slowly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers fought so …………………….. that the enemy troops fled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bravely",
                "timidly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you walk ………………………. you will not reach there in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slowly",
                "slow",
                "fast"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}